mg.co.za 2004-06-10

# Mail & Guardian Online:

|   
---  
BREAKING NEWS  
  
WEEK IN PICTURES|   
INSIGHT  
  
REGULARS  
  
PARTNER SITES  
  
|   
---|---  
|  | **Find old friends**  
Choose your school's Province/Country and click on the first letter of your school  
A B C D E F G H I J K L M N O P Q R S T U V W X Y Z  |  |   
|   
  
|   
---|---  
|  | **Career search**  
Search South Africa's #1 job listings and career advice site.  
**Find me a job!** |  |   
|   
  
|   
---|---  
|  | **Digital M &G**   
Have your M&G newspaper delivered via the web, anywhere in the world, directly to your PC!  
|   
  
|   
---|---  
|  |  **M &G Awards 2004**  
**New:** Investing in the Future Awards 2004 recognises companies and organisations that have contributed to society by investing in the communities of our country. Enter now!  

|  |   
|   

**Find your match now!**  
I am a: |   
---|---  
Looking for: |  |   
Age Range: | to  

 **QUICK LINKS**  
  
\- Today's weather  
\- [Games](http://www.mg.co.za/Content/pd.asp?sa=13)  
\- [Notes & Queries](http://www.mg.co.za/Content/pd.asp?sa=9)

 **SERVICES**  
  
\- 

\- [News & Lotto SMS alerts](http://www.mg.co.za/sms)  
\- [Subscription queries](http://www.mg.co.za/Content/l3_f.asp?o=558)  
\- [Free news for your site](http://www.mg.co.za/Content/l3_f.asp?o=19914)  
\- [Book accommodation](http://www.mg.co.za/travel/)  
\- [Find old friends](http://www.sareunited.com/sar_mg.html)  
\- [Find a job](http://www.mg.co.za/Content/pd.asp?sa=11)  
\- [Find a date](http://mg.datingbuzz.com/s/find/search.php)  
\- [Send flowers](http://www.netflorist.co.za/agent.asp?affID=100000331&cwpg=1)  
\- [Place an advert](http://www.mg.co.za/Content/l3_f.asp?o=565)  
|  |   **PRIVACY POLICY**  
---  
**Privacy Policy**  

  * _Mail &Guardian Online_ and M-Web (" _Mail &Guardian_" or "we" or "us" or "our") respect your privacy and is committed to protecting it. 
  * We recognise your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you may share with us (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number). 
  * In general, you can browse sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We do track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyse this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous. 
  * Some of our Web pages utilise "cookies" so that we can better serve you with more tailored information when you return to our site. "Cookies" are used to enhance your interactive experience and generally improve our service to you. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. 
  * We store information you supply in personalising your use of the services. 
  * We protect subscriber information from outside parties by storing it in a fully-secured database. 
  * You may update personal information at any time by using the personalise function. 
  * You acknowledge, that in the interests of improving personalisation and service efficiency, we may, under controlled and secure circumstances, share your personal information with some of M-Web's affiliate companies who provide content to this portal. 
  * In all other cases, the only information we will ever disclose to third parties (e.g.: advertisers) is aggregate information about our users. 
  * Aggregate information will never identify you. It only identifies the user population in general terms, e.g.: 52% males visit a particular site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content and/or services of sites linking out of the our BFA network or for personally identifiably information made available by you or another third party in or through the forums of the _Mail &Guardian_.

|  |
